kyosho.com 2004-12-04

# Hobbico Privacy Statement

* * *

Effective January 1, 2002.

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. This privacy statement applies to all manufacturer web sites maintained by Hobbico, Inc. 

Our site uses a form for visitors to request information and services as well as make suggestions for improving our products and web site. We collect visitor's contact information (like their e-mail address) where appropriate. Contact information is only used to get in touch with the visitor when a response from us is necessary (like a request for warranty information). This personal information is not shared with outside parties. 

Domain names and IP addresses may be logged for statistical and administrative purposes only. Our site may use a temporary "cookie" when a visitor accesses an interactive page, such as dealer locator.

No financial or other sensitive information is collected anywhere on our site. 

We do not collect the personal information for children under the age of 13. We are prohibited from conditioning a child's participation in an activity on the child disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary. In cases where we have inadvertently collected personal information of a child, the parent can always review this information, choose to have this information deleted from our records and refuse to permit further collection or use of this information. 

We respect your privacy and work diligently to protect it. 

* * *

Copyright © 2002-2004 Hobbico, Inc. [Terms of Use](http://www.hobbico.com/tos.html)  
All rights reserved. Do not duplicate or redistribute in any form.
